<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE locale SYSTEM "../../../../../lib/pkp/dtd/locale.dtd">

<!--
  * plugins/generic/webOfScience/locale/en_US/locale.xml
  *
  * Copyright (c) 2024 Clarivate
  * Distributed under the GNU GPL v3.
  *
  * Localization strings
  -->

<locale name="en_US" full_name="U.S. English">

  <message key="plugins.generic.wosrrs.displayName">Web of Science Reviewer Recognition Service Plugin</message>
  <message key="plugins.generic.wosrrs.description">This plugin allows you to post reviews to Web of Science.</message>

  <message key="plugins.generic.wosrrs.button.submitExportReview">Export my review to Web of Science</message>
  <message key="plugins.generic.wosrrs.button.publishedReview">This review has been exported to Web of Science</message>
  <message key="plugins.generic.wosrrs.button.completeReview">You must submit your review before it can be exported to Web of Science</message>

  <message key="plugins.generic.wosrrs.notifications.settingsUpdated">Settings updated</message>

  <message key="plugins.generic.wosrrs.settings.connection">Connection</message>

  <message key="plugins.generic.wosrrs.settings.journalTokenRequired">Please enter the correct journal token for your Web of Science Reviewer Recognition Service integration.</message>
  <message key="plugins.generic.wosrrs.settings.auth_tokenDescription">The Authorization token for the specified account (you can find that on https://publons.com/api/v2/ under Token).</message>
  <message key="plugins.generic.wosrrs.settings.authTokenRequired">Please ensure that your Authorization token is correct.</message>
  <message key="plugins.generic.wosrrs.settings.journalToken">Journal Token</message>
  <message key="plugins.generic.wosrrs.settings.auth_token">Authorization Token</message>
  <message key="plugins.generic.wosrrs.settings.journalTokenDescription">The journal token used to export reviews to Web of Science</message>

  <message key="plugins.generic.wosrrs.confirmation.title">Send your review to Web of Science</message>
  <message key="plugins.generic.wosrrs.confirmation.termsAndConditions">
    <![CDATA[
      <p>
        You have chosen to export your review to Web of Science. <br> <a href="https://clarivate.com/wp-content/uploads/dlm_uploads/Product-Terms_3.4-Web-of-Science-Reviewer-Recognition.pdf" target="_blank">Terms and conditions</a>.
      </p>
    ]]>
  </message>

  <message key="plugins.generic.wosrrs.notice.title">Export review to Web of Science</message>
  <message key="plugins.generic.wosrrs.notice.explanation">
    <![CDATA[
      You will be able to export your review to <a href="https://clarivate.com/products/scientific-and-academic-research/research-publishing-solutions/reviewer-recognition-service/reviewer-recognition-for-reviewers/" target="_blank">Web of Science</a> on tab 4 once you have submitted your review.
    ]]>
  </message>

  <message key="plugins.generic.wosrrs.export.successful">The review has been successfully exported</message>
  <message key="plugins.generic.wosrrs.export.duplicate">This review has already been exported to Web of Science</message>
  <message key="plugins.generic.wosrrs.export.error">Error exporting review to Web of Science</message>
  <message key="plugins.generic.wosrrs.export.error.400">There is a permissions error. Please contact the web administrator for this journal.</message>
  <message key="plugins.generic.wosrrs.export.error.500">There is a server error. Web of Science is not responding, please try again in 10 minutes.</message>

  <message key="plugins.generic.wosrrs.export.claimReview">Claim review</message>
  <message key="plugins.generic.wosrrs.export.next.autoClaimed">Your review has been auto-claimed on Web of Science.</message>
  <message key="plugins.generic.wosrrs.export.next.partnerEmailed">Your journal has emailed you with a link to claim this review or you can click on the button below.</message>
  <message key="plugins.generic.wosrrs.export.next.reviewerEmailed">Web of Science has emailed you with a link to claim this review or you can click on the button below.</message>
  <message key="plugins.generic.wosrrs.export.next.setAutoClaim">To skip this step in future please select "Automatically add reviews from partnered journals" in your Web of Science Researcher Profile settings.</message>
  <message key="plugins.generic.wosrrs.export.next.linkClick">You have opted out of receiving Web of Science emails, to claim this review you must click the link below.</message>

  <message key="plugins.generic.wosrrs.export.error.alreadyExported">Review has already been exported to Web of Science</message>
  <message key="plugins.generic.wosrrs.export.error.reviewNotSubmitted">You must submit your review before you can export it to Web of Science</message>
  <message key="plugins.generic.wosrrs.export.error.invalidUser">Invalid OJS login details</message>

  <message key="plugins.generic.wosrrs.settings.info">
    <![CDATA[
      <p>
        <a href="mailto:reviewservices@clarivate.com">Email us</a> to start giving your reviewers recognition. We'll provide you the Authorization and Journal Token(s) needed to complete the next steps.
      </p>
      <p>
        To enable the plugin fill in the fields below
      </p>
    ]]>
  </message>

  <message key="plugins.generic.wosrrs.settings.ps">
    <![CDATA[
      <p>
        Once you have enabled the plugin, reviewers will have the option to get recognition for their review on the review submission page.
      </p>
      <p>
        If the reviewer opts in to get recognition, data will be securely transmitted to Web of Science upon the review's submission. The reviewer will receive an email (at the email address they registered with the journal) containing a link to claim their review.
      </p>
      <p>
        Reviewers will be asked to log into Web of Science and the review will be added to their account. Reviewers can select "Automatically add reviews from partnered journals" in their Web of Science Researcher Profile settings to eliminate this step.
      </p>
      <p>
        Web of Science won't publish review content unless both the journal and the reviewer allow it.
      </p>
    ]]>
  </message>

</locale>
